Guide to the Jack Shoemaker Papers, 1992-1994
Department of Special Collections
- Series VII: Pantheon Manuscripts
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Range: Literature to Laughter" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Reaction to a Letter" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "A Report of my Visit to...Edna Ford" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "The Reunion" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Revised Statement of Policy" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "The Right to Write" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "The Room" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "The Second Time Around" (reprint) (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "To Settle One's Love" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Single Passage, 1936" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "(Some Other Picnics)" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Slander Suit" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Snow White and Rose Red" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Stay Me, Oh Comfort Me" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 37)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Taxi Drivers" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 38)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Tea With Agamemnon" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 39)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Through a Glass Darkly" (reprint) (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "The Time I Didn't Do It" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 41)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "The Tiny Blade of Nutmeg" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 42)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "To the Victor" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 43)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Tom" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 44)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Tout Droit, M'sieur" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 45)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "The Trap Door" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 46)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "A Tribute to Extravagance" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 47)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Troy" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 48)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Two Kitchens in Provence" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 49)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Two Octaves" (TMs reprint) (Box 38, Folder 50)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "The Unswept Emptiness" (TMs reprint) (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Vevey, Suisse" (TMs reprint) (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Veni, Vidi, Bibi" (TMs reprint) (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "A View of the Delta Queen" (TMs reprint) (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "The Weather Within" (reprint) (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "What Happened and What Did Not" (TMs reprint) (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "What I Know of Butch" (TMs reprint) (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "What I Remember About My Cousin Ronald" (TMs reprint) (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "When Wrong be Right" (TMs reprint) (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "Wine is a Word" (TMs reprint) (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: "The Zany Period..." (TMs reprint) (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - M.F.K. Fisher, uncollected writing: from folder marked "Dillwyn's": Grandmother reminisciences (TMS and AMs reprints) (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Anne Lamott, Bird By Bird: first draft (Nov. 11, 1993; titled "Anxiety Judgement Doom Joy: Notes on Writing and Life" (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Anne Lamott, Bird By Bird: draft Jan. 3, 1994; titled "The Agony and the Ecstasy" (Box 39, Folder 14-15)
  - Anne Lamott, Bird By Bird: draft Feb. 3, 1994; with editorial commentary, Anne Lamott, Bird By Bird: page design and cover art (os, 2) (Box 39, Folder 16-18)
  - Anne Lamott, Bird By Bird: miscellaneous production notes (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Anne Lamott, Operating Instructions: (nd; titled "One Year") (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Anne Lamott, Operating Instructions: final uncopyedited draft Aug. 10, 1992 (under "Sam's Book") (Box 40, Folder 3-4)
  - Anne Lamott, Operating Instructions: edited house copy, nd (Box 40, Folder 5-8)
  - Anne Lamott, Operating Instructions: setting MS (Box 40, Folder 9-12)
  - Gene Logsdon, At Nature's Pace (as "Essays"; original reprints) (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Gene Logsdon, At Nature's Pace (first developmental pass) (Box 41, Folder 1-3)
  - Gene Logsdon, At Nature's Pace: copyedited draft (Box 41, Folder 4-5)
  - Gene Logsdon, At Nature's Pace: cut material (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Gene Logsdon, At Nature's Pace: supplemental materials (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Gene Logsdon, At Nature's Pace: page design (os, 2)
  - Gary Paul Nabhan, Songbirds, Truffles and Wolves (as "Pilgrims on a Changed Trail"): Ms with Shoemaker marginalia (Box 41, Folder 8-10)
  - Gary Paul Nabhan, Songbirds, Truffles and Wolves (as "Pilgrims on a Changed Trail"): manuscript transmittal forms, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Gary Paul Nabhan, Songbirds, Truffles and Wolves (as "Pilgrims on a Changed Trail"): notes Jan. 29, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Gary Paul Nabhan, Songbirds, Truffles and Wolves (as "Pilgrims on a Changed Trail"): selected proofs, Mar. 16, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Nabhan, Songbirds: galleys (Box 42, Folder 1-3)
  - Gary Snyder, No Nature: from preliminary folder marked 'edited' (TMs reprints) (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Gary Snyder, No Nature: from folder marked "leave-outs" (TMs reprints) (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Gary Snyder, No Nature: from folder marked "No Nature: New Poems" (TMs) (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Gary Snyder, No Nature:"Bubbs Creek Haircut" and "The Blue Sky" (TMs originals) (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Gary Snyder, No Nature: setting Ms (Box 42, Folder 8-10)
  - Gary Snyder, No Nature: page design (os, 2)
  - Gary Snyder, No Nature: galleys (Box 43, Folder 1-4)
- Series VIII: Personal Collection
  - address book, with interleaved pages of earlier address book (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Syllabus 1, Art of the Wild Seminar, April 1993: (reprints, bound) (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Syllabus 1, Art of the Wild Seminar, April 1993: syllabus 2 (reprints, bound) (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - The Awakening of the West: Zen Buddhism and Western Culture Parallax Press uncorrected proof copy (bound) (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Thinking Green! Parallax Press uncorrected proof copy (bound) draft 1, pub. date April 1994 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Thinking Green! Parallax Press uncorrected proof copy (bound) draft 2, pub. date June 1994 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Series IX: Photos
  - William Bronk (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Elizabeth Cox (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Ross Feld (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Amy Gerstler (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Edmund Jabes (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Wes Jackson (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Jed Perl (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Gilbert Sorrentino (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Megan Staffel (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Fred Turner (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Luisa Valenzuela (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Lawrence Weschler (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - mixed folder; from collection marked "Enduring Seeds" (Box 45, Folder 13)